buyandsell.ie 2013-06-15

# Buy and Sell anything in Ireland | Easy to use – BuyandSell.ie

Buzreel Limited, trading as BuyandSell ("BuyandSell" or "we") respects and protects your right to privacy in relation to your interactions with this website. We have adopted the following policies to safeguard your personal information and to protect its confidentiality. 

Any information which is provided by you to BuyandSell via this website or otherwise will be treated in accordance with the terms of the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 and/or such amending or replacement legislation as may be adopted in Ireland from time to time. We encourage you to read this Privacy Statement before using this website. If you do not read or if you disagree with any aspect of the Privacy Statement, you should not use this website. Your use of this website signifies your agreement to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Statement. 

### Access by children

If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parents/guardian's permission before submitting personal data to this website. Users without this consent should not submit any personal data to this website.

### Collection and Use of Information

When registering with BuyandSell you will be asked to provide certain personal information, such as name, email address, phone number, date of birth, etc. Personal data which we collect from you will only be used for the purposes for which it was provided by you. BuyandSell will not release your personal data to any third parties without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating information and collecting debts, unless we reasonably believe that we are required to do so by operation of law. BuyandSell retains the right at all times to contact you in relation to the services provided on this website. If at any time after giving us this information you decide that you no longer wish us to hold or use this information, or in the case that the information becomes out of date, you are free to notify us, and we will endeavour to remove or rectify the information promptly. We use your personal information to identify you as a customer, to process your advertisement, to verify credit or other charge card details and to deliver relevant information to you in connection with your advertisement. Personal information about you will not be given or sold to any third parties for use in its marketing or solicitation without your consent. We don't collect or keep your personal data unless it is necessary for the above purposes(s) nor do we keep your personal data for longer than is necessary. You also acknowledge and agree that in certain circumstances we may be obliged to disclose personal information relating to you to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend the rights of BuyandSell, and/or our customers. BuyandSell reserves the right to transfer information (including your Personal Information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of BuyandSell, a subsidiary or line of business associated with BuyandSell.

### Link to Third Party Sites

You should also be aware that where you link to another website from this website, that BuyandSell has no control over that other website. Accordingly, BuyandSell cannot guarantee that the controller of that website will respect your privacy in the same manner as BuyandSell.

### Access to your Personal Information

You have the right to request a copy of the information which we hold about you (for which we may charge you a small fee) and to have inaccuracies in the information corrected. You can change your registration information including unsubscribing for communications by selecting the "update registration" button from the main menu on this website. Please submit requests to our

### Your Use of Others Information

You agree that, with respect to other users' personal information which you obtain through the BuyandSell website, or as a result of any related communication or transaction, BuyandSell hereby grants you a licence to use this information only for: (i) BuyandSell related communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages; or (ii) any purpose that the data subject expressly agrees to after you tell them the purpose you would like to use this personal information for. 

Under no circumstances (except without the users express consent) may you disclose personal information about another user to any third party without the consent of BuyandSell and/or the consent of that user. You agree that other users may use your personal information to communicate with you in order to facilitate transactions as set out in BuyandSell. Except as otherwise set out in this Privacy Statement this policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information that BuyandSell collects from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties (for example to buyers or sellers on this website or to other websites throughout the internet) a different privacy statement may apply to their use or disclosure of the information disclosed to them. As BuyandSell cannot control the privacy policies of third parties, you should be aware that you will be subject to the privacy policies of that third party.

### Use of Technical Information

While using this website, you may have the opportunity to send us information relating to you such as through the "Contact" page or by placing an advertisement online or where you send emails. By choosing to participate in these, you will be providing us with some level of personal information relating to you. This information will only be used by BuyandSell for the purpose for which it was provided by you or for verification purposes and statistical analysis. We use Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology. If your browser supports SSL then any personal data that you send will be protected during transmission by encryption. Due to the nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee the protection of your personal data and therefore we are not responsible for any loss or damage resulting to you when the website is used. You should be aware that each time you visit a website, two general levels of information about your visit can be retained. The first level comprises statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate and non-individual specific basis of all browsers who visit the website and the second is information which is personal or particular to a specific visitor who knowingly chooses to provide that information. The statistical and analytical information provides us with a general and non-individual specific information about the number of people who visit this website; the number of people who return to the website; the pages that they visit; and where they were before they came to the website and the page in the website at which they exited. This information helps us monitor traffic on a website so that we can manage the website's capacity and efficiency. This type of non-personal information and data can be collected through the standard operation for internet servers and logs as well as "cookies".

### Cookies

Cookies are small data files that a website can use in order to recognise visitors who revisit a website so as to facilitate their ongoing access to and use of the website. Cookies are used by websites to store visitor's user settings and therefore most browsers are initially configured to accept cookies. Typically, cookies involve the assigning of a unique number to the visitor. You should be aware that BuyandSell is unable to control the use of cookies or the resulting information by other third parties such as advertisers or parties hosting data for BuyandSell. One simple way to prevent the use of cookies is to activate the facility which is available in most web browsers that enables a user to deny or accept cookies. However, you should realise that certain cookies may be necessary in order to provide you with certain features such as the customised delivery of certain information. Further information can be found by clicking here

### Disclaimer

Buyandsell, its directors, employees, servants and agents, affiliates or other representatives and their respective parent and subsidiary companies, shall not be liable in respect of any claims, emergencies, demands, causes of action, damages, losses, expenses, including without limitation, reasonable legal fees and costs of proceedings arising out of or in connection with the use and/or dissemination of personal information relating to you in accordance with this privacy policy and your consents.

### Amendments

BuyandSell reserves the right in its sole discretion to amend this privacy policy at any time, and you should regularly check this privacy policy for any amendments.

**Congratulations** close

### Your Voucher has been accepted. Your Ad will be live within 15 minutes.

You will receive an email in the next 15 minutes, confirming that your Ad is live on BuyandSell.ie If you have not received your confirmation within this time, please check your spam filter.   
To avoid messages reaching spam in the future, you should add   
[noreply@buyandsell.ie](mailto:noreply@buyandsell.ie) to your address book. 

If you have any queries about how we proof ads, please contact our support team
